<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Testemonials on Doula, Emilie Young</title>
    <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Testemonials on Doula, Emilie Young</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:59:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zoe</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/zoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:59:27 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/zoe/</guid>
      <description>Emilie was essential to my birth.&#xA;Labor is hard and it was one of the biggest workouts of my life. My husband was my mental support and Emilie was my labor foundation. She kept me hydrated, not waiting for me to ask for water but offering me water with a straw every so often. She tracked down my protein shake and even managed to find me some fruit to snack on when we had forgotten our own snacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sadie</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/sadie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:58:02 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/sadie/</guid>
      <description>Emilie was referred to us for her sibling doula services from a local midwife and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been happier with her support! I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know sibling doulas were a thing! We had a 19 month old at the time of our homebirth and with no family support in the area we needed someone to take care of our toddler during the labor and delivery. Emilie came over a few weeks before the birth to meet our toddler and us, and learn about her routine, the house layout, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/madison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:54:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/madison/</guid>
      <description>Emilie was with us a few nights a week for 3 months after my second son was born. While hiring a night doula was an investment, it was the best decision our family made for the postpartum period. I had been dreading the fourth trimester after a difficult time with my first baby. Emilie made the experience completely different and way better. Having sleep throughout the week allowed me to really enjoy my time with my new baby (and also with my toddler!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dana</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/dana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/dana/</guid>
      <description>Emilie is fantastic! I was nervous to give birth, but she made me feel capable and confident. She provided a wealth of information that helped me understand what to expect, think through my preferences and limits, and process my fears. Her enthusiastic and positive demeanor allowed me to relax and focus on my body and my baby. And when my birth didn’t go at all as planned, I felt prepared for this possibility and thankful to have her there for advice and to support my decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bailey</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/bailey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/bailey/</guid>
      <description>We had the pleasure of working with Emilie as a postpartum doula and she is an absolute angel. So great with our baby, and so supportive to me when I was having a really hard time with lack of sleep and PPD. Emilie is a wonderful listener, and there if you need to talk, or she will also just melt into the background to take care of your newborn and laundry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andi</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/andi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/andi/</guid>
      <description>Emilie was beyond all expectations and became the bedrock of our family immediately. We had our twins very early, after a lengthy NICU stay, they arrived home medically fragile and with challenges. As mom, I also had a dangerous delivery, and came home with limitations myself. Emilie came into our lives with our twins at a time we needed someone we could trust, rely on, nurture us all, and help us get thru a very difficult period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angela</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/angela/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/angela/</guid>
      <description>I had the pleasure of working as co-doula with Emilie. I highly recommend her as either a birth or postpartum doula. She is both light-hearted and wise. She brings such a warmth to her work! Emilie shared excellent resources in the prenatal appointments and helped the client make an easy-to-read birth plan, which all the nurses loved!&#xA;During the birth, Emilie provided continuous encouragement. She suggested different positions and provided gentle comfort measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buthaina</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/buthaina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/buthaina/</guid>
      <description>Emilie came into my life when I was very depressed and in need of any kind of support.&#xA;Having had to deliver my first baby alone in the US, and away from my husband and family, through a c-section too, I had to go through a lot on my own which drained me physically and emotionally. I was in pain and depressed the whole time, and cried everyday.&#xA;Emilie&amp;rsquo;s presence in my life changed everything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McKenzie</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/mckenzie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 15:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/mckenzie/</guid>
      <description>I was Emilie&amp;rsquo;s first birth mama. It was my first time giving birth. She owned the doula title with gentle, yet assertive guidence. Her ability to assess my needs as I was internally processing my labor was astounding. It was a festival birth of 3-4 days of labor and 3 1/2 hrs of pushing and she was there by my side every step. She led my team and advocated for me with grace and diligence, all the while being mindful of my ideals.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
