<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Doula on Doula, Emilie Young</title>
    <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/tags/doula/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Doula on Doula, Emilie Young</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:54:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/tags/doula/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Madison</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/madison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:54:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/madison/</guid>
      <description>Emilie was with us a few nights a week for 3 months after my second son was born. While hiring a night doula was an investment, it was the best decision our family made for the postpartum period. I had been dreading the fourth trimester after a difficult time with my first baby. Emilie made the experience completely different and way better. Having sleep throughout the week allowed me to really enjoy my time with my new baby (and also with my toddler!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dana</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/dana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 15:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/dana/</guid>
      <description>Emilie is fantastic! I was nervous to give birth, but she made me feel capable and confident. She provided a wealth of information that helped me understand what to expect, think through my preferences and limits, and process my fears. Her enthusiastic and positive demeanor allowed me to relax and focus on my body and my baby. And when my birth didn’t go at all as planned, I felt prepared for this possibility and thankful to have her there for advice and to support my decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McKenzie</title>
      <link>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/mckenzie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 15:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zothsu.github.io/emilieYoung/testemonial/mckenzie/</guid>
      <description>I was Emilie&amp;rsquo;s first birth mama. It was my first time giving birth. She owned the doula title with gentle, yet assertive guidence. Her ability to assess my needs as I was internally processing my labor was astounding. It was a festival birth of 3-4 days of labor and 3 1/2 hrs of pushing and she was there by my side every step. She led my team and advocated for me with grace and diligence, all the while being mindful of my ideals.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
